petty worthless. If you don’t have Sync Connect that is. I mean, do I really need an app that will show me how much gas I left in my truck’s gas tank from inside my house or wherever?!!? That’s kinda stupid but this is essentially what you’re left with if you’re without Sync Connect. It shows you how much gas you have left. Otherwise, I could care less about being notified through an app about recalls, I get those by mail and more than likely it’ll be on the ABC Lightly News anyway. If I need an app to figure out where I parked, then I probably shouldn’t be driving anyway. To check for gas prices ? ... Nah...But wait... if I can see that I have about an eighth of a tank of gas left via this very handy app while I’m sitting in my den then I can decide from this app where the I’m going to buy gas tomorrow... wonderful. Bottom line is that Sync Connect should have been made more widely available by Ford in their vehicles so that this app would have a more practical use. And I truly love Ford- I’ve have been leasing 2 vehicles since 1995.
This app is nice and works pretty well but it does seem to crash a lot leaving me without access to its features like remote start. Unfortunately, when it does crash I cannot tell immediately that is has except that it tells me something isn’t right. Then I try to log out and back in to try it again several times unsuccessfully so I just move on with my day at that point. Another thing that doesn’t make much sense is that there are two message streams when my car is communicating with me. I’ll get a message about washer fluid being low in my messages and then I'll also get a little yellow dot on the “my vehicle” tab telling me the same thing and it won’t clear out until I refill the washer fluid even if I check the message. It would also be nice if the settings in my car are used when remote starting the car like turning on my seat warmer. I like the app and use it regularly but these are improvements that would make it better. Thanks!
This app lets you start your car, lock/unlock, check your battery, fuel & oil levels which is great. I haven’t experienced any of the crashing others have. However the app does seem to work slow which is the reason I gave it 4 out of 5 stars. It lags getting to the features you need and can take 1-4 minutes to actually start your car. It also doesn’t turn my heated seats on from the remote start but this isn’t much of an issue since my seats heat up quickly any way. It does however seem to have a far reach when trying to start your vehicle which is a bonus if you park far away from a building everyday like I do for work. Overall very happy with the app just wish it worked faster.
After the update it can't locate my car at all, the feature is disabled. It also takes a much longer to refresh the information about the car. Couple times the app started my car without me clicking on a Start button. Total disappointment (
At last Ford fixed the problem. Now my mustang can effortlessly connect with Ford Pass. And I am not gonna lie, I am kind of impressed with the software. With the new look and updated app this app is "my thing" now for everyday. Double thumbs up.
It's a an OK app but still has some bugs. After the last update the $ in my service history changed to a British Pound sign, also the print link for coupons does nothing. Also hope for more content in the near future.
Its handy. But I had a recall on my truck. Work has been done byt the ap still ahows that it is beeded syill. How do I clear the notice? That is a big glitch in my opinion. And the chat feature is never available.
I have never been this impressed with any app!! This is the best experience that I have ever had.
Since the latest (09/17/18) update, app defaults to "shutting off (engine) in < x min" when first opened, even while someone else is out driving the vehicle. Something is seriously amiss here. Did anyone actually test this updated version of the app before release?
It let's you know if there are recalls on your vehicle. You can pay your bill through it. Track your parking spot. Find gas stations. Easy to use.
Setup was fine. Locator seems to work ok. Remote start, lock/unlock works. Gas prices reported were old and not accurate. Maybe get data from gasbuddy would help? Showing status of locked or unlocked would be nice so you can see if you forgot to lock your vehicle. I'll keep using and change rating accordingly for future updates.***updated... better layout, but otherwise same issues.